Norton, Joseph L.; Papers ua902.006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Joseph L. Norton Papers
1940-1998
1950-1983
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Norton, Joseph L., 1918-
ua902.006
14 cubic ft.
The Joseph L. Norton Papers include notes, correspondence, memoranda, newsletters, publications, and other materials documenting Norton's work as a SUNY Albany professor, a counselor, a teacher, and an activist in the gay community.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
The Joseph L. Norton Papers were donated to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 1996 by Joseph Norton.
Biographical History
Joseph L. "Joe" Norton was born on September 6, 1918 in Albany, New York. He received a B.A. in French (1940) and an M.A. in Personnel Psychology (1941), both from St. Lawrence University, and a Ph.D. in Counseling Psychology from Syracuse University (1950). He married in 1947 and had two children. In 1971, he divorced and shortly afterwards came out publicly as gay.
After brief spells in insurance and teaching high school as well as a stint in the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers from 1942-1945, Norton began his academic career as Assistant Professor and Counselor at Michigan State University in East Lansing, Michigan from 1949-1951. From 1951 to 1953 he was Associate Professor of Psychology and Director of Counseling and Placement at Knox College in Galesburg, Illinois. Norton spent ten years as Professor of Educational Psychology at Alfred University in Alfred, New York before coming to SUNY Albany (now the University at Albany, SUNY) to be a Professor of Education in 1963. He remained in that position until his retirement in 1983. Norton's early teaching and research interests lay mainly in educational psychology and vocational placement, and later he became interested in LGBT counseling issues and sex education.
In addition to his academic work, Norton was a prominent figure in the gay rights movement within his community and profession. He helped to found the Capital District Gay & Lesbian Community Council (now known as the Pride Center of the Capital Region); the AIDS Council of Northeastern New York; the National Caucus of Gay and Lesbian Counselors of the American Association of Sex Educators, Counselors and Therapists; and the Caucus of Gay Counselors of the American Personnel and Guidance Association. He served as advisor to the Gay Liberation Front in New York State (1971–1972) and was a member of the Board of Directors of the National Gay Task Force (1976–1978). Norton also was involved with the Association of Gay, Lesbian and Bisexuals in Counseling; the National Gay & Lesbian Task Force; the New York State Coalition of Gay Organizations; the National Association of Gay Psychologists; and Interweave, an LGBT organization affiliated with the Unitarian Universalist church. He also frequently gave talks and presentations to professional, school and community groups in the Capital District and beyond.
Joe Norton died on May 18, 2011, at the age of 92.
Scope and Contents
The Joseph L. Norton Papers include notes, correspondence, memoranda, newsletters, publications, and other materials, with the bulk dating from the mid-1940s to the mid-1990s.
Series 1 consists of papers relating to Joe Norton's research and publications, including notes, drafts, correspondence with publishers, and reprints.
Series 2 contains notes, correspondence, memoranda, newsletters, conference programs, and other materials related to Joe Norton's involvement in professional organizations, chiefly in the fields of psychology and counseling.
Series 3 includes materials related to Joe Norton's work as a member of the faculty at SUNY Albany. Subseries 1 contains teaching materials such as syllabi, lecture notes, and exams. Subseries 2 consists of student papers and dissertation proposals. Subseries 3 relates to other academic duties such as committee and departmental work, and contains notes, correspondence and memoranda.
Series 4 contains subject files. The first subseries consists of materials relating to gay rights activism organizations and includes notes, memoranda, newsletters, and other materials. (Note that groups involved with LGBT issues within the psychology and counseling profession are included in Series 2.) Subseries 2 consists of correspondence. Subseries 3 contains reference material in the form of clippings, publications, informational literature, newsletters, and notes on topics related to LGBT issues and rights, mental health, sex education, and other areas of interest collected by Joe Norton.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Research and Publications, 1941-1989, Undated
Series 2 - Professional Organizations, 1948-1998, Undated
Series 3 - Faculty Papers, 1940-1983, Undated
Subseries 3.1: Class Materials, 1952-1983
Subseries 3.2: Student Work, 1947-1980, Undated
Subseries 3.3: University Service and Administrative Material, 1940-1983, Undated
Series 4 - Subject Files, 1946-ca. 1996, Undated
Subseries 4.1: Activism, 1970-ca. 1996, Undated
Subseries 4.2: Correspondence, 1951-1980, Undated
Subseries 4.3: Reference Material, 1946-1991, Undated
Series 4, Subseries 2 and 3 are arranged alphabetically. All other series and subseries are arranged chronologically.
Social Activists and Public Advocates; Senior Citizens; Neighborhood and Community Associations; Medicine and Health Care; Human Sexuality and Gender Identity; Albany, New York; Counseling; Educational counseling; Sexuality; Correspondence; Newsletters; Files by subject; UAlbany Faculty & Alumni Papers; State University of New York at Albany
- Research and Publications, 1941-1989, Undated; 1; 1 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Chonological
  Contents:
  This series contains papers that were written by Joe Norton, including early research, published and unpublished materials, book reviews, and materials relating to research that led to written work.
  - Adjustment Inventory, 1941; ca. 1940 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 1)
  - St. Lawrence University Placement Bureau, 1941 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 2)
  - Projective Devices, 1947 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 3)
  - Dissertation, 1953 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 4)
  - Commencement Speeches & Misc. Speeches, 1956; 1960; Undated (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 5)
  - Some Doubts about Current Usage of Defense Mechanisms, 1957 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 6)
  - "Help Wanted:" The Teens Tackle Vocational Development, 1958 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 7)
  - Comparison of Occupations Graded Papers, 1959 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 8)
  - A Diary Report on Frequency of Masturbation, 1959 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 9)
  - Counseling the Disabled, 1960 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 10)
  - A Study of the "Estimates of Worker Trait Requirements", 1961 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 11)
  - IBM Data Processing Computer Fortran / Facts about Mental Illness pamphlet, 1962-1965 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 12)
  - An Introduction to Validity and Reliability, 1962-1964 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 13)
  - Swimming Cross-Country, 1964 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 14)
  - What of Courage in our Schools, 1964 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 15)
  - Questionnaire, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 16)
  - Some Characteristics… A review of four research studies, 1968 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 17)
  - Current Status of the Measurement of Vocational Maturity, 1968; 1969 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 18)
  - Current Status of Research on Vocational Development, 1970 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 19)
  - Affective Sexual Awareness Preparation Program, 1974 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 20)
  - Book Reviews, 1975; 1978-1984; 1994 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 21)
  - The Homosexual and Counseling, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 22)
  - Counselor Education Trial Project Proposal, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 23)
  - Teaching About Homosexuality in Psychology Courses, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 24)
  - Counseling Men: Book Chapter, 1979 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 25)
  - Special Populations and the Helping Professional: Book Chapter, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 26)
  - Kelly's "Sexuality: The Human Perspective" test questions, 1980 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 27)
  - Integrating Lesbian/Gay Issues into Counselor Education, 1981 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 28)
  - Published & Unpublished Manuscripts, 1981; 1989; Undated (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 29)
  - Survey of Lesbian and Gay Counseling Centers, 1982 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 30)
  - Survey on Variability of Erections, 1982 (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 31)
  - A Review of Reliablility: Its Meaning and Problems for Measurement, Undated (Box 1 (1-Research and Publications), Folder 32)
- Professional Organizations, 1948-1998, Undated; 2; 2 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical by subject
  Joe Norton was an active member of professional organizations and committees within those organizations. Materials here include his communication within committees, publications produced by organizations, and subscriptions.
  - American Association of Sex Educators and Counselors, 1969-1977 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 1)
  - American Association of Sex Educators, Counselors and Therapists, 1972-1979 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 2)
  - American Association of Sex Educators, Counselors and Therapists: Gay-Bi Caucus, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 3)
  - American Association of Sex Educators, Counselors and Therapists: Gay-Bi Caucus, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 4)
  - American Association of Sex Educators, Counselors and Therapists: Gay-Bi Caucus, 1978-1982 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 5)
  - American Association of Sex Educators, Counselors and Therapists: Eleventh National Sex Institute, 1978 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 6)
  - American Mental Health Counselors Association, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 7)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association Pamphlets, Undated (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 8)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Caucus of Gay Counselors, 1976-1980; Undated (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 9)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Caucus of Gay Counselors, 1976-1979 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 10)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Caucus of Gay Counselors, 1977-1979 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 11)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Caucus of Gay Counselors, 1979-1981 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 12)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Senate Vote, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 13)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Caucus of Gay Counselors: CGC Newsletter, 1976-1978 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 14)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: National Caucus of Gay and Lesbian Counselors Caucus Comments, 1978-1986 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 15)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Caucus Comments and AGLBIC Newsletter, 1986-1994 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 16)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Professional Preparation Standards, 1967 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 17)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Rules Committee, 1971-1978 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 18)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association: Special Aging Project, 1978 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 19)
  - American Psychiatric Association: San Francisco Annual Meeting, 1980 May (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 20)
  - Association for Counselor Education and Supervision Committee on Standards, 1965; 1967; Undated (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 21)
  - Association for Counselor Education and Supervision, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 22)
  - Association for Counselor Education and Supervision: Survey Results, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 23)
  - Association of Counselor Educators Accreditation Papers, 1965 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 24)
  - Association of Counselor Educators of NYS, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 25)
  - Association of Counselor Educators of NYS Annual Meeting, 1967 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 26)
  - Association of Gay Psychologists, 1974-1978 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 27)
  - Association of Gay Psychologists, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 28)
  - Association of Lesbian & Gay Psychologists, 1981; 1986-1988 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 29)
  - Binghamton Conference Hotel Research, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 30)
  - Career Education and the World of Work Colloquium, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 31)
  - Certification and Education of School Counselors, Undated (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 32)
  - Committee on Parent and Family Life Education, Undated (Box 1 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 33)
  - Conference for Counselor Educators, 1960; 1963 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 1)
  - Confidentiality and the Guidance Counselor, 1969-1971 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 2)
  - Counselor Competence and Social Concerns, 1971 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 3)
  - Counselor Training, 1956-1958 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 4)
  - Counselor Training Accreditation, 1955-1968 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 5)
  - Counselor Training Workshop, 1959 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 6)
  - Counselor's Guides, 1972-1976 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 7)
  - Educational Testing, 1953-1961 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 8)
  - Gay Academic Union Conference, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 9)
  - Gay Academic Union, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 10)
  - Gay Aids for Counselors, 1980 May (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 11)
  - Gay/Lesbian/Bisexual Interest Group, 1987-1990 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 12)
  - Gay Rights Activism, 1970-1976 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 13)
  - Guidance Directors and Counselor Trainers: Annual Conference, 1953-1954 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 14)
  - Guidance and Personnel Services Research Tools, Undated (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 15)
  - Guidance Personnel Programs, Undated; 1968-1970 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 16)
  - Health Education and Welfare Club, 1982 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 17)
  - Human Sexuality Group, 1974; 1977 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 18)
  - Improving the Effectiveness of the College Teacher, 1951 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 19)
  - International Work Conference for Counselor Educators, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 20)
  - Measurement of Vocational Development Conference, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 21)
  - National Association of Guidance Supervisors and Counselor Trainers, 1954; 1956-1957 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 22)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 23)
  - National Gay Health Coalition, 1977-1981 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 24)
  - National Gay Health Coalition, 1981-1983; 1998 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 25)
  - National Gay Health Directory, 1979; 1982 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 26)
  - National Gay Health Education Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 27)
  - National Register of Health Service Providers in Psychology, 1978 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 28)
  - New York State Counselors Association, 1962-1967 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 29)
  - New York State Personnel and Guidance Association, 1967-1975 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 30)
  - Occupational Questionnaire Correspondence, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 31)
  - Old AIDS Phone Lists, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 32)
  - The Process of Certification for Guidance, 1964 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 33)
  - Present Status of Educational Psychology and Psychologists, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 34)
  - Pruett Press Invoice, 1967 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 35)
  - Steering Committee for Better Mental Health in Albany County, 1967-1970 (Box 2 (2-Professional Organizations), Folder 36)
- Faculty Papers, 1940-1983, Undated; 3; 5.6 cubic ft.
  - Class Materials, 1952-1983; 3.1; 2 cubic ft.
    Contains materials used by Joe Norton in preparation for teaching classes. Materials include notes, exams, worksheets, papers, and research related to building syllabi.
    - Psychology 101 & 102, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 1)
    - Psychology 145, 1953 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 2)
    - Psychology 103 & Educational Psychology 125, 1953; 1954 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 3)
    - Psychology 111, 1954 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 4)
    - Psychology 101 & Psychology 501, 1954-1956; 1960 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 5)
    - Introduction to Guidance Exams, 1954-1961 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 6)
    - Education 619, 1955-1962 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 7)
    - Education 619, 1955-1962 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 8)
    - Comprehensive Examination, 1955-1963 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 9)
    - Intelligence & IQ, 1956 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 10)
    - Psychology 113, 1956 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 11)
    - Mental Health Research, 1956-1965 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 12)
    - Psychology 531, 1958 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 13)
    - Introduction to Guidance, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 14)
    - Education 511, 1960 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 15)
    - Education 511, 1960 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 16)
    - Education 618, 1960 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 17)
    - Psychology 511, 1960 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 18)
    - Psychology Class Exams, 1960-1963 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 19)
    - Education 511, 1962 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 20)
    - Research for Teaching, 1962; 1966-1970 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 21)
    - Research for Teaching, 1962; 1967; 1970-1973 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 22)
    - Education 326B & Education 229, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 23)
    - Education 325, 1964; 1967 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 24)
    - Education 21, 1965 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 25)
    - Education 229, 1965 (Box 1 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 26)
    - Educational Psychology 200, 1966-1969 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 1)
    - Advanced Techniques of Counseling, 1967 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 2)
    - Education 325, 1967 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 3)
    - Sensitivity Training, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 4)
    - Educational Psychology 200, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 5)
    - New York State Tests, 1969-1973 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 6)
    - Student Groups - EGPS 608, 1970 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 7)
    - Standardized tests, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 8)
    - ECPS 604, EPGS 605, Education 124, 1970; 1974 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 9)
    - Tests and Evaluation Forms, 1970; 1975; 1977 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 10)
    - Student Personnel Program in Higher Education, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 11)
    - Vocational Choice - EGPS 604, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 12)
    - Career Psychology Mobile Seminar, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 13)
    - Individual Counseling - ECPS 601A, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 14)
    - Seminar in Counseling in the Helping Professions - ECPS 627, 1973-1977 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 15)
    - ECPS 603A & ECPS 601, 1975 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 16)
    - Notes for 602, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 17)
    - Career Development - 604, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 18)
    - The Homosexual Imagination in Literature, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 19)
    - Value Exercises, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 20)
    - Psychology of Individual Behavior - 600, 1977 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 21)
    - ECPS 601A Exam, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 22)
    - Educational Psychology 503, 1978-1980 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 23)
    - Educational Psychology 503, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 24)
    - ECPSD 601B, 1979 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 25)
    - Human Sexuality for the Helping Professions - EPSY 503, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 26)
    - Individual Counseling - ECPS 601A, 1979; 1983 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 27)
    - ECPS 602, 1980 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 28)
    - Spring 1980 Notes (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 29)
    - Institute: Counseling About Sexuality - ECPY 687, 1980 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 30)
    - Fundamental Techniques of Group Counseling, 1982 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 31)
    - Introduction to Counseling - ECPY 601A, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 32)
  - Student Work, 1947-1980, Undated; 3.2; 1.6 cubic ft.
    Contains student papers, internship evaluations, dissertation proposals, dissertation drafts, and some exams
    - Sam L. Witryol, 1947 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 1)
    - William A. Carpenter, 1955 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 2)
    - Donald Stead, 1955 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 3)
    - George N. Graine, 1956 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 4)
    - Miriam Kay, 1962 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 5)
    - Eileen Kelly, 1964 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 6)
    - Practicum Critiques, 1964 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 7)
    - R. Velachovio, 1966 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 8)
    - Sabi Abu-Libden, 1967 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 9)
    - Practicum Critiques, 1967 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 10)
    - Joseph Pascale, 1967 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 11)
    - Paul B. Boyce, 1968 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 12)
    - Practicum Critiques, 1968 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 13)
    - Kenneth York, 1968 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 14)
    - Arreed Barabasz, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 15)
    - Lucie Barber, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 16)
    - Alexander LaRocco, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 17)
    - J. J. McGrath, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 18)
    - Salvatore Pappalardo, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 19)
    - Practicum Critiques, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 20)
    - Edmund Rozecki, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 21)
    - Gerald Seen, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 22)
    - Dell N. Thompson, 1969 (Box 3 (3-Faculty Papers), Folder 23)